Guide to the Alex Harris photographs and papers, 1970-2015 RL.10060
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Dream of a House, 2011; 61 prints 2 boxes
  - Reynolds Price's entryway and stairway to the upstairs, 2011 (Box 77, Print RL.10060-P-0510)
    DSC_3934
  - Detail from a portrait of Reynolds Price #2, 2011 (Box 77, Print RL.10060-P-0511)
    DSC_4226
  - Reynolds Price's bedroom bookshelf #1, 2011 (Box 77, Print RL.10060-P-0512)
    DSC_4616
  - Reynolds Price's office bookshelf #1, 2011 (Box 77, Print RL.10060-P-0513)
    DSC_4188
  - Reynolds Price's office #3, 2011 (Box 77, Print RL.10060-P-0514)
    DSC_4415
  - Reynolds Price's office #4, 2011 (Box 77, Print RL.10060-P-0515)
    DSC_4026
  - Reynolds Price's living room #4, 2011 (Box 77, Print RL.10060-P-0516)
    DSC_3705
  - Reynolds Price's office bookshelf #2, 2011 (Box 77, Print RL.10060-P-0517)
    DSC_4194
  - Reynolds Price's office #5, 2011 (Box 77, Print RL.10060-P-0518)
    DSC_3912
  - Reynolds Price's kitchen #2, 2011 (Box 77, Print RL.10060-P-0519)
    DSC_3664
  - Windowsill, Reynolds Price's home, 2011 (Box 77, Print RL.10060-P-0520)
    DSC_3646
  - Reynolds Price's office #6, 2011 (Box 77, Print RL.10060-P-0521)
    DSC_4471
  - Reynolds Price's office #7, 2011 (Box 77, Print RL.10060-P-0522)
    DSC_4478
  - Reynolds Price's office #8, 2011 (Box 77, Print RL.10060-P-0523)
    DSC_4177
  - Anteroom to Reynolds Price's office and bedroom, 2011 (Box 77, Print RL.10060-P-0524)
    DSC_4453
  - Wall of Heroes, Reynolds Price's bedroom, 2011 (Box 77, Print RL.10060-P-0525)
    DSC_4207
  - Reynolds Price's office #9, 2011 (Box 77, Print RL.10060-P-0526)
    DSC_3825
  - Reynolds Price's bedroom #1, 2011 (Box 77, Print RL.10060-P-0527)
    DSC_4343
  - Reynolds Price's living room #5, 2011 (Box 77, Print RL.10060-P-0528)
    DSC_3694crop
  - Reynolds Price's bedroom bookshelf #2, 2011 (Box 77, Print RL.10060-P-0529)
    DSC_4625
  - Reynolds Price's bedroom bookshelf #3, 2011 (Box 78, Print RL.10060-P-0530)
    DSC_4627
  - Reynolds Price's office #10, 2011 (Box 78, Print RL.10060-P-0531)
    DSC_3849
  - Reynolds Price's dining area #3, 2011 (Box 78, Print RL.10060-P-0532)
    DSC_3768
  - Reynolds Price's kitchen and bedroom view, 2011 (Box 78, Print RL.10060-P-0533)
    DSC_4291
  - Reynolds Price's office #11, 2011 (Box 78, Print RL.10060-P-0534)
    DSC_3836
  - Reynolds Price's office #12, 2011 (Box 78, Print RL.10060-P-0535)
    DSC_4484
  - Reynolds Price's office #13, 2011 (Box 78, Print RL.10060-P-0536)
    DSC_4037
  - Reynolds Price's office bookshelf 3, 2011 (Box 78, Print RL.10060-P-0537)
    DSC_4656
  - Reynolds Price's exercise/gallery room #2, 2011 (Box 78, Print RL.10060-P-0538)
    44-DSC_4390
  - Reynolds Price's bedroom #2, 2011 (Box 78, Print RL.10060-P-0539)
    DSC_4331crop
  - Reynolds Price's exercise/gallery room #3, 2011 (Box 78, Print RL.10060-P-0540)
    DSC_4122
  - Reynolds Price's home #2, 2011 (Box 78, Print RL.10060-P-0541)
    DSC_5654
  - Reynolds Price's office #14, 2011 (Box 78, Print RL.10060-P-0542)
    DSC_4022
  - Reynolds Price's kitchen #3, 2011 (Box 78, Print RL.10060-P-0543)
    DSC_4100
  - Reynolds Price's dining area with office view, 2011 (Box 78, Print RL.10060-P-0544)
    DSC_4296
  - Reynolds Price's living room #6, 2011 (Box 78, Print RL.10060-P-0545)
    DSC_3995
  - Reynolds Price's office #15, 2011 (Box 78, Print RL.10060-P-0546)
    DSC_4375
  - Shrine between Reynolds Price's office and bedroom, 2011 (Box 78, Print RL.10060-P-0547)
    DSC_3668
  - Reynolds Price's kitchen #4, 2011 (Box 78, Print RL.10060-P-0548)
    DSC_3655
  - Anteroom to Reynolds Price's office and bedroom #2, 2011 (Box 78, Print RL.10060-P-0549)
    55-DSC_4673
  - Reynolds Price's living room #7, 2011 (Box 78, Print RL.10060-P-0550)
    DSC_4662
  - Reynolds Price's office #16, 2011 (Box 78, Print RL.10060-P-0551)
  - Reynolds Price's living room bookshelf, 2011 (Box 78, Print RL.10060-P-0552)
    DSC_4600
  - Detail from a portrait of Reynolds Price #3, 2011 (Box 78, Print RL.10060-P-0553)
    DSC_4125
  - Detail from a portrait of Reynolds Price #4, 2011 (Box 78, Print RL.10060-P-0554)
    DSC_3970
  - Detail from a portrait of Reynolds Price #5, 2011 (Box 78, Print RL.10060-P-0555)
    DSC_3967
- Publicity and Audiovisual Materials, 1971-2003, 3 boxes
  Scope and Contents note
  Contains paper and a/v materials related to exhibits and publications featuring Harris's work in documentary photography. This series also includes several audio recordings of presentations by Harris. Recordings related to specific documentary projects are described with their related materials in the Project Files Series.
  Conditions Governing Access note
  [Original audiovisual materials are closed to use. Use of these materials may require production of listening or viewing copies. Please contact Research Services before coming to use this collection.]
  - Printed materials, 1971-2003
    Contains copies of publications which feature Harris's photography; one contains an essay on his work. Additionally, includes one folder of thumbnails and captions of particular photographic documentary projects, 1998-2001.
    - Aperture, 1978 and 1989, 2 issues (Box 26)
    - Innovations, 2001-2002, 4 issues (Box 26)
    - El Contemporani, 2001 (essay on Harris) (Box 26)
    - Yale Alumni Magazine, 1971 (Box 26)
    - Brochures, Cordoned Heart and Gertrude Blom, 1984 and undated (Box 26)
    - Other brochures, 1993-2000 and undated (Box 26)
    - Printed pages of thumbnail images and captions from Harris's photographic collection at Duke, 1998-2001 (Box 26)
    - Exhibition catalog, Les Suds profonds de l'Ãmerique--Alex Harris, Clarence John Laughlin, Ralph Eugene Meatyard: collection le Pavillon des Images, 2010 (Box 60)
      Produced by Gilles Mora, Paris, Democratic Books. Also includes leaflet from exhibition and undated [2010] gift note from Alex Harris. Exhibition date: 2010 Oct. 21-2011 Jan. 30.
  - Audio recordings, 1982-2003 and undated
    Recordings of Harris from a 1993 presentation given at the National Humanities Center, an exhibit reception at Duke University in 2003, a discussion with individuals in an exhibit in 2003, and undated recordings of a National Public Radio broadcast and a lecture(?) on South Africa. Titles taken from original cassette labels, with some information supplied by the archivist. Arranged chronologically.
    Lectures and speaking engagements related to Harris's photographic projects and publications, including A World Unsuspected: Portraits of Southern Childhood; A New Life: Stories and Photographs from the Suburban South; and South Africa: The Cordoned Heart project, are found in their respective subseries in the Project Files Series.
    [Original audiovisual materials are closed to use. Some use copies are available and are noted. Otherwise, access to materials requires production of listening or viewing copies. Please contact Research Services before coming to use this collection.]
    - National Humanities Center (NHC) lecture: The Art of Documentary Photography, #247, circa 1993 (Box 27, Audio-cassette RL_10060_C_012)
    - NHC lecture: Culture in Focus, #653, circa 1993, 2 copies (Box 27, Audio-cassette RL_10060_C_013)
      [Listening copy available in Box 28.]
    - Harris's presentation at the opening reception of his exhibit, Alex Harris Photographs, 1998-2000, Images From the David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library, September 24, 2003 (Box 27, Audio-cassette RL_10060_C_018)
    - Listening copy of NHC lecture (audiocassette), "Culture in Focus" by Harris (Box 28)
    - Innovations: The Audio Collection (RV Care-A-Vanners), 2003 (Box 85, Audio-cd RL10060-CD-0001-0004)
    - DRAG interview, NPR, Chris Hoskens & Eleni Boussios, undated (Box 85, Audio-cassette RL10060-CS-0031-0032)
      2 copies?
    - Beyond the Front Line: South Africa, 1980-86, Undated (Box 85, Audio-cassette RL10060-CS-0033)
  - Video recordings, 1984,1996, 2007 and undated
    One VHS video cassette and one DVD documenting class activities and a lecture. There is another VHS video cassette with an interview with Harris regarding an exhibit on Mississippi, and two Umatic cassettes on Gertrude Blom.
    [Original audiovisual materials are closed to use. Use copies are noted when available, otherwise access copies must be created. Please contact Research Services before coming to use this collection.]
    - Xunan--The Lady (film about Gertrude Blom), 1984 January 25 (Box 85, Video-cassette RL10060-UM-001-002)
      Two Umatic videocassettes.
    - "AGO AME made by the students of CA 180S, Duke University, Fall 1996, Film and Video Program and Dept. of Cultural Anthropology," VHS video cassette, 1996 (Box 65)
    - Use copies of "AGO AME" video and "The Idea of Cuba" lecture by Harris (Box 65)
    - "The Idea of Cuba--Alex Harris Lecture," Nasher Museum, DVD, 2007 Nov. 16 (Box 65)
    - Mississippi Self(?), Undated (Box 85, Video-cassette RL10060-VHS-0002)
      10-minute interview with Harris regarding Mississippi photographs. VHS video cassette.
- Correspondence, 1972-2006 and undated, 17 boxes
  Correspondence, drafts, grant applications, research notes, photographs, printed materials, proofs, publicity, and other materials produced during Harris's work on a variety of books, conferences, exhibitions, and academic activities from the mid-1970s through 2006. Some projects are covered in considerable depth, including the following: early history of the Duke University Center for Documentary Studies; Wendy Ewald and the project that eventually became the Literacy Through Photography Program; photographer Paul Kwilecki's first book, Understandings; Harris's work with Robert Coles and Helen Levitt on her In the Street: Chalk Drawings and Messages New York City, 1938-1948; and various projects involving South African photographers (see scope notes for specific boxes). Other books and exhibitions represented in this series include: I Shall Save One Land Unvisited: Eleven Southern Photographers (1978); The Last and First Eskimos (1982); The Old Ones of New Mexico (various editions); Red White Blue and God Bless You: a Portrait of Northern New Mexico (1992); and River of Traps: a Village Life (1990). Arranged alphabetically by correspondent or topic.
  - Abram-Bios, 1973-1992 and undated, 36 folders (Box 29)
  - Black photography-CDS, 1980-1991 and undated, 30 folders (Box 30)
  - CDS Board-Coffey, 1979-1991, 20 folders (Box 31)
  - Coles-Dietz, 1972-1992 and undated, 28 folders (Box 32)
    Materials include correspondence and publicity for The Cordoned Heart exhibition.
  - Doc book-Ewald, 1976-1991 and undated, 25 folders (Box 33)
  - Ewald-Gallery 10, 1980-1992 and undated, 22 folders (Box 34)
    Materials include seventy-five of Harris's 35mm slides and related negatives of John Hope Franklin, 1990 June-July.
  - General correspondence, 1973-2006 (Box 79)
    Topics include fundraising for various projects and travel, exhibitions, and various individual photographers.
  - General correspondence-ICP (International Center of Photography), 1976-1991 and undated, 38 folders (Box 35)
  - ICP-Ledochowski, 1978-1990 and undated, 21 folders (Box 36)
    Materials include manuscripts and correspondence with photographer Paul Kwilecki on his first book, Understandings. See also related materials filed under the book's title. Some items removed to Oversize Materials.
  - Leger-Lyndhurst, 1980-1990 and undated, 20 folders (Box 37)
  - Lynnemeir-Mora, 1979-1992 and undated, 34 folders (Box 38)
    One folder, A.J. Meek, removed for preservation.
  - Morgan-Resume, 1977-1992 and undated, 43 folders (Box 39)
  - Rhodenbaugh-Smith, 1981-1992 and undated, 32 folders (Box 40)
  - Smithsonian-South Africa, Cordoned Heart, 1981-1991 and undated, 13 folders (Box 41)
    Materials include: correspondence with Omar Badsha and other photographers; publicity and photographic materials for various South Africa projects such as Beyond the Barricades, The Cordoned Heart and The Transported of Kwandebele For the last title, see also materials filed under David Goldblatt.
  - South Africa, Friends of Photography-Trachtenberg, 1981-1991 and undated, 21 folders (Box 42)
    Materials include; correspondence and publicity materials for the South Africa Documentary Photography Fellowship Program; transcripts of interviews with South African documentary photographers and with South African journalist Allister Sparks.
  - Trask-Young, 1975-1990 and undated, 36 folders (Box 43)
  - Photographs, various projects, 1972-1991 and undated, 5 folders (Box 44)
    8x10" format prints and negatives removed from correspondence folders for flat storage. Includes work on projects with Gertrude Blom, Robert Coles, the photographs of Aden Field, and publicity photographs for The Cordoned Heart.
- DoubleTake Files, 1991-1998 and undated, 6 boxes
  Files consist chiefly of correspondence with several hundred authors, photographers, and staff members during the first few years of publication of the magazine DoubleTake. Recordings derive from organizational meetings and various talks by DoubleTake founders such as Robert Coles.
  - DoubleTake files, 1986-1993 and undated
    Related materials may be found in the DoubleTake Records, 1908-1999 (bulk 1993-1999), also held in the Rubenstein Library. Materials about the magazine's founding can be found under files titled Editorial Prospectus; Whitney Ellsworth (a publishing consultant); Publication--Early Correspondence; and Quail Roost conference, and in other folders. See also the recordings in this series. Arranged alphabetically by name or topic.
    - Ackerman-Crosland, 80 folders (Box 45)
    - Cummings-Exploris, 36 folders (Box 46)
    - Farmer-Kellam, 65 folders (Box 47)
    - Keohane-Mickiewicz, 57 folders (Box 48)
    - Microscopic-Quail Roost, 44 folders (Box 49)
    - Race-Zagajewski, 94 folders (Box 50)
  - DoubleTake recordings, 1986-1993 and undated
    A group of eight recordings, six of which document meetings and retreats conducted in the early 1990s to discuss creation of the magazine eventually known as DoubleTake. Two microcassettes from 1986 feature Robert Coles discussing the Center for Documentary Studies. No transcripts have been discovered, but material on the early history of the magazine is present in this collection. Several tapes may derive from the same meeting at Quail Roost Retreat in 1993, although with slight variations in labeling and dating. Tapes are arranged chronologically. "MC" denotes microcassettes, "C," audiocassettes.
    [Originals closed to use. Listening copies must be made. Please consult with a reference archivist before coming to use this item.]
    - "R. Coles on Documentary Studies," 1986 Jan. 27 (Box 62, Audio-cassette RL_10060_MC_019)
    - "R. Coles on Documentary Studies," 1986 Jan. 27 (Box 62, Audio-cassette RL_10060_MC_020)
    - "Bob Coles/Whitney Ellsworth," 1992 May 4 (Box 62, Audio-cassette RL_10060_C_025)
    - "Bob Coles/Alex Harris Q.R. [i.e., Quail Roost] #1," undated [1993 May 5?] (Box 62, Audio-cassette RL_10060_C_026)
    - "#3 Quail Roost Retreat, Whitney Ellsworth, Alex Harris, et al.," 1993 May 5 (Box 62, Audio-cassette RL_10060_C_027)
    - "Bob on magazine," undated (Box 62, Audio-cassette RL_10060_C_028)
    - "DoubleTake conv. [conf.?]," undated (Box 62, Audio-cassette RL_10060_C_029)
    - "DoubleTake meeting," undated (Box 62, Audio-cassette RL_10060_C_030)
- Project Files, 1970-2013 and undated, 17 boxes
  Articles, correspondence, grant applications, manuscripts, notes, photographic materials, printed materials, research notes, slides, tape recordings, and other documents derived from various books and related exhibitions and symposia on which Harris has worked as curator, editor, organizer, or photographer. The bulk of the materials derive from the following three books and related projects: Gertrude Blom: Bearing Witness (1984); A New Life: Stories and Photographs from the Suburban South (1997); A World Unsuspected: Portraits of Southern Childhood (1987); and from South Africa: The Cordoned Heart, (1986) a project on South African photographers documenting apartheid, conducted with Omar Badsha, Bruce Payne, Margaret Sartor, and others. Also includes the book projects Idea of Cuba, Arrivals and Departures, River of Traps, Why We Are Here, This Fabulous Loneliness, and Visions in the Dark for Aperture. There are two large sets of oral history interviews on cassette tapes in this series, deriving from Harris's work with anthropologist Blom, and from his work with South African photographers.
  - Arrivals & Departures, 1999-2003 and undated
    Comprises materials related to the book Arrivals and Departures: The Airport Pictures of Garry Winogrand, which Harris edited with Lee Friedlander. Includes correspondence; research; working files; photocopies, slides, and prints of images; along with drafts and mock-ups of the book.
    - Correspondence, 1999-2002 and undated (Box 67, Folder 1)
    - Gary Winogrand research, 2001 and undated (Box 67, Folder 2)
    - Working files, 2002-2003 and undated (Box 67, Folder 3)
    - Working files for introduction, undated (Box 67, Folder 4)
    - Xerox of images: 1. good print, 2. print needs work, 3. no print, undated (Box 67, Folder 5)
    - Gary Winogrand airport slides, undated (Box 67, Folder 6)
    - Gary Winogrand airport slides, duplicates and rejects, undated (Box 67, Folder 7)
    - Draft 1, undated (Box 68, Folder 1)
    - Draft 2, undated (Box 68, Folder 2)
    - Dummy mock-up, undated (Box 68, Folder 3)
    - Slides of book, undated (Box 68, Folder 4)
    - Work prints, undated, 2 folders (Box 72)
    - Photographs, undated (Box 68, Folder 5)
  - A New Life, 1993-1998 and undated
    Biographies of authors and photographers, correspondence, finances and contracts, and printed materials for A New Life: Stories and Photographs from the Suburban South (1997). Arranged alphabetically by topic. Also includes a recording of Harris speaking about his work, circa 1997.
    - A New Life files, 17 folders (Box 53-54)
    - Inside The Arts: Alex Harris - A New Life, circa 1997 (Box 27, Audio-cassette RL_10060_C_011)
  - A World Unsuspected, 1984-1987 and undated, 3 boxes
    Manuscripts, recorded lectures, correspondence, copy-edited typescripts, printed materials, and other project files for Harris's book, A World Unsuspected: Portraits of Southern Childhood (1987). Also included here are preparations for a conference at the Lyndhurst Foundation in Chattanooga. Arranged with individual authors's manuscripts first, followed by topical categories in chronological order.
    - A World Unsuspected project files, 54 folders (Box 55-57)
    - "Alex Harris--A World Unsuspected" [Side A], undated; "Backward Glances Closing" [Side B], 1988 Apr. 23 (Box 27, Audio-cassette RL_10060_C_010)
    - "A World Unsuspected," undated, 4 audiocassettes (Box 27, Audio-cassette RL_10060_C_014-C_017)
  - The Idea of Cuba, 2004-2005
    Comprises three versions of Harris' book, The Idea of Cuba, including two drafts and a small-scale final facsimile created by John Hill.
    - The Idea of Cuba, daft 1 (Box 66)
    - The Idea of Cuba, draft 2, 2 folders (Box 66)
    - The Idea of Cuba, Final facsimile (Box 66)
  - River of Traps, 1991 and undated
    Comprises a manuscript draft for the book River of Traps, along with cover mockups, all undated.
    - Manuscript, undated (Box 69, Folder 1)
    - Cover mock-ups, 1991 and undated (Box 69, Folder 2)
  - This Fabulous Loneliness, 2012-2013
    Comprises two drafts of the book This Fabulous Loneliness, featuring photographs of Reynolds Price's residence.
    - First draft, 2012 (Box 71)
    - Second draft, 2013; 2 folders (Box 71)
  - Visions of the Dark, 1978
    - Copy of APERTURE volume, 1978 (Box 74)
  - Why We Are Here, 2012
    Comprised solely of guide prints for the book Why We Are Here: Mobile and the Spirit of a Southern City.
    - Guide prints, 2012; 3 folders; Linear Feet (Box 70)
  - Gertrude Blom Project Files, 1970-1987 and undated
    Articles, recorded interviews, correspondence, grant applications, manuscripts, research notes, card files, and other materials related to projects on anthropologist, journalist, and photographer Gertrude Duby Blom, who documented the culture and struggles of Mexican indigenous peoples such as the Lacandón. Materials center around Harris's work with Blom on the book Gertrude Blom: Bearing Witness (1984) and the related exhibition at the International Center for Photography, also 1984, co-curated by Harris and Margaret Sartor. Arranged alphabetically by topic. Photos of indigenous tribes, probably from this period, are also found in Box 57.
    The Rubenstein Library also holds a small collection of Blom's photographic prints of the Lacandón.
    [Original audiovisual materials are closed to use. Listening copies are available. Please contact Research Services before coming to use this collection.]
    - Blom project files, 22 folders (Box 51-53)
    - Gertrude Blom project manuscript reproductions, undated (Box 84)
    - Mexico: small black-and-white photographs of indigenous tribes and bi-racial people (Lacandón, Ladinos, and others), circa 1983, 3 folders (Box 57)
  - Gertrude Duby Blom Oral History Interviews, 1982 July and undated
    Eight of the cassettes are interviews conducted by Alex Harris; the ninth cassette features Blom speaking at a conference. Titles are transcribed from original cassette labels, with some additional expansion/information supplied by archivist.
    [Listening copies available in Box 28.]
    - G. Blom 7/3/82-conference; 7/4/82-childhood [Side 1]; G. Blom 7/4/82 childhood; 7/5/82 Italy, Germany [Side 2] (Box 27, Audio-cassette RL_10060_C_001)
    - G. Blom - political yrs 7/4; Europe 7/5, Mexico 1939 [Side A]; 7/5-7/6/82 Early Days Lacandones; 2 Jacinto, Bor [Side B] (Box 27, Audio-cassette RL_10060_C_002)
    - 7/6/82, Missionaries, early Mexico; changes (?), deforestation [Side A]; deforestation, change culture; Na Bolom, Bor & Kin [Side B] (Box 27, Audio-cassette RL_10060_C_003)
    - 7/9/82--Bor and Kin 7/10/82 [Side A]; 7/11/82 Trudi [Blom] on photography, politics--world situation [Side B] (Box 27, Audio-cassette RL_10060_C_004)
    - 7/12, Politics and Frey Bartolomé; 7/13 Education, Franz -- Anthropology (?) [Side A]; 7/14 Trudi [Blom] on Women [Side B] (Box 27, Audio-cassette RL_10060_C_005)
    - 7/14, Woman as photog [photographer]; 7/15 Chan K'in & roman [Side A]; 7/15 Chan K'in & Rivers (?); 7/16 (Box 27, Audio-cassette RL_10060_C_006)
    - G. Blom 7/15/82 (57) 7 on conference [Side A]; G. Blom on Photos 7/20 [Side B] (Box 27, Audio-cassette RL_10060_C_007)
    - Trudi on Photos 7/20 (elec. goes off) [Side A]; Trudi on photos 7/20 [Side B] (Box 27, Audio-cassette RL_10060_C_008)
    - "Blum--Trudi's talk/conference" [Side A]; "Gertrude Blom" [Side B], undated (Box 27, Audio-cassette RL_10060_C_009)
    - Use copies of interviews with Gertrude Duby Blom (Box 28)
  - South Africa: The Cordoned Heart, circa 1985-1986
    Audiocassettes and micro cassettes of interviews with many of the twenty photographers represented in the Rubenstein Library's South African Documentary Photography Collection, curated by Alex Harris during his work on the project "South Africa: The Cordoned Heart," which resulted in a book published in 1986. Interviews were conducted mainly by Alex Harris and Margaret Sartor. The tapes are mainly undated, but transcripts place them between October 1985 and July 1986. Also includes presentations by Alex Harris and Bruce Payne and others.